<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ahisahar Pretel Rodríguez on Ahisahar Pretel Rodríguez</title>
    <link>https://approdriguez.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ahisahar Pretel Rodríguez on Ahisahar Pretel Rodríguez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016 Ahisahar Pretel Rodríguez</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Trainer</title>
      <link>https://approdriguez.github.io/project/android-trainer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://approdriguez.github.io/project/android-trainer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Create an Android app for help coaches and users to realize power trainings using generic purpose devices, like a smartphone and a smartwatch. For realize the measurings of the trainings it uses the watch accelerometers and gyroscope. These sensors send the data to the smartphone. After it is processed it is shown in a user friendly user interface .&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arduino Coil Gun</title>
      <link>https://approdriguez.github.io/project/arduino-coil-gun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://approdriguez.github.io/project/arduino-coil-gun/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Using an Arduino to control and display the different stages between a coil gun, charged and fire. Close the charge stage once the capacitors are charged, display the info at the LCD screen and using a relay control the fire button. Code and instructions available soon on GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/approdriguez/arduino-coil-gun&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://github.com/approdriguez/arduino-coil-gun&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Granada Game Jam</title>
      <link>https://approdriguez.github.io/project/granada-game-jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://approdriguez.github.io/project/granada-game-jam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have always loved games. I enjoy playing games but I haven&amp;rsquo;t made one and wanted to create some content and share it with the community. So we arranged a four people team and decided to use Godot engine (an open source game engine).
After the brainstorm, we decided to make a survival-type in a undiscovered world where some insects spawn and try to kill you. Feel free to play the game and contribute!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jesusgn90/game-jam-granada-2017&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://github.com/jesusgn90/game-jam-granada-2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
